Hello, everybody.
How we doing?
So, we had a little issue today with your old Arthur.
Arthur, Arthur, Arthur.
Did you even catch it?
He had to be removed from the panel.
Because he stopped behaving himself.
Ink has been okay
Let me change my light too. I'm just a nice
Hey Trump just like
Yeah
Stop it up
It's not stopping.
Oh, well, just had a flash for a little bit.
Hey, what's up, Nick?
How's your day, guys?
It's June 19th, 619th.
Okay, so there's a show called Don't Hug Me I'm Scared.
And just, they made,
I think there's probably 10 episodes now,
but they made five like several years ago.
Label it made after Sesame Street and some really something else really weird. You've ever heard of it
But they have this calendar a simple calendar in the room and it always says June 19
So I don't know maybe June 19th is significant day. Hey, what's up Lola? What's going over here?
Hi vanilla, hi Nick. How was everybody?
Come on in come on in
oh there we go my light oh wait i fixed it look
isn't it beautiful though it's like for such an inexpensive light what an effect
what an amazing effect i hope i didn't just turn off my stream hold on so we went around
to the uh and you bit into your wet crocs lake oh you went around the lake
In your wet crocs first time ever. I can't read today. I don't know. I'm not my vision is going
Hope you're doing good at night is this it's Thursday night. Oh good finally. I
Love Thursdays and waiting for Thursday for a little bit
We eat yeah, I do got some weed. I do have I mean have some I have a beer, too
I'm just gonna take it kind of slow tonight
But I'm really proud of myself because I did clean most of this room
I just need to do the laundry and put the dishes in the dishwasher, which I will do very shortly and
Organize my bedroom
Yeah, finally I fixed it. Yeah
It's like I just finally got
Like yesterday I did half of it and then like last night I did half of it too.
I don't know, it just looks better. Okay enough the tables. I brought the furniture and this is
sitting outside forever. Cats are seeming happier. Hey what's up kitty cat? I got Lola, I got Rudy.
I think Trix is over there eating. Hi.
Bong yeah, let's do a bong hit. Well, I don't have a bong. Oh, yeah, the bong hit. Yeah, so easy got me a bong
I do have a bong easy got me a bong. I don't have a weed. That's a problem. And so I don't have a flower. I don't have
but but I have a
Have a vape. It looks like a pregnancy test. It probably has a third left of it in there
The cool thing about this light is I can just like, you know, put it in a different color and my shirt will look different so I can
stop, I can just like, you know, buy one white shirt and just
use that from now on.
Now, it's a really cool little light. It was just, it was just like, oh,
sorry, it's bright. It was just like five bucks, or six bucks on, uh,
on, what's that website? Teemu, which is,
it arrived really quickly.
Might want to check out T-Move for some stuff. I know they also have they do have like I know the tarot cards
They have some or like knockoff cards
about other decks that are out there, but
You know if you want to like, you know get a few extra decks just to play around with
You know, it's not gonna be as high quality big ink and stock, but it's probably the same printing
But uh, you know, they're they're pretty good deal to I know cards are very the tarot cards are very expensive very expensive
$20 to $30 $20 to $40 actually
The pack there's not very many for under $20. Hey, Eleanor, Eleanor's over here. Eleanor
Eleanor here Eleanor guys
Being it okay, let's do it
Somebody up. I'm sorry. I missed somebody with somebody up on. Let's see. I miss I didn't see I'm sorry
Let's distract that you know hitting my my pipe. Okay
So I also got the couch. I got everything back on the couch one viewer. I know it's not sad
It's actually it is one. Oh my god. That is very sad. I am the embers. It's on its way out, huh?
Well, you know what?
Even Donald Trump went bankrupt a couple times. Look at him. He's doing fine. So I have faith
Do you believe in miracles? Oh, there's zero people in the room. It's okay. It's okay guys
It's okay
I'm down to hang out check out the meaning of tarot cool YouTube channel and cool website
I'm pretty cool devices. Oh, okay. Isn't it called meaning of tarot? Oh, look it up. Hey, what's up?
Fucking lucky. Thank you. Yeah, I've 10 I have 10 people. I thought it said one and now I have 10 people
I'm at the hump of YouTube panels. I
Don't know I I think I'm decent I good
YouTube panels especially since I just started pretty like you know within the last year
I just started doing the panels last year
So oh the museum. Okay. Me. Oh museum of terror. Oh my god. I'm so out of it today museum of tarot. We're over
Oh, so there's a
YouTube called that can you put?
Pull black RG card if you if you would like if you would like what I need his permission. I
don't want to like
Give a message without him wanting it, but if you'd like a card RG to say number between one and ten
And I'll pull a card for you. Oh, it's time to build and stick
Anybody else can do too. Okay. Ducky
Disney villains deck
Okay, nor seven, okay
I'm just gonna I'm gonna pull one, you know a card with that, you know
Shuffle seven times and then I'll pull another card and we'll see what those two cards say okay one two
Three
four
five
six
Seven okay, there's one I'll pull this one for you, too. Okay, I didn't look okay
So villains deck okay, oh, okay
Yeah captain hook. I mean I've seen this this work comes before it's like basically the gist of the card is you know
I have to accept everything offered to you and you know
He certainly rejected a few things but also
You know, they're maybe you've rejected a few you've been offered a few things you kept rejecting them
I think the next one is the one you've been waiting for it. It's like I thank you or maybe you've even given up
Your thing. Oh after three times. I'm not gonna wait for anymore. It's it. I think the fourth time is he's happy there
Okay, I don't even need to look in the book. That's that's what it means. Okay
Okay, eight of wands. Okay eight of wands. There's eight of wands
What do we have here? It looks like
Did anybody know what movie this is from?
I'm not 100% sure.
Some of them are from newer movies.
It looks like they're touching some magic wands together.
This is the card of communication,
specifically swift and strong communication.
So if you're waiting for something
and that's probably gonna be regarding that last cup
that's the fourth cup that's being handed to you.
Okay, that's Fantasia.
You're gonna be connecting with this information very quickly whether it's through email
Post-a-mail phone call or even a spiritual guide or dream. There's a message coming for you. Okay?
So and if you've been waiting for
Something here, you know, you hooks a pirate, right? So you got you got the maybe a little pirate blood in you, too. Okay?
Hope you enjoyed
You think that Asia yeah
I haven't seen Fantasia in quite a while.
I like the Sorcerers of Prentice.
And a lot of, I love the, some of the,
I just know some of the imagery from the movie.
I don't remember the music exactly.
Oh, you're welcome.
You're very welcome.
Oh, cool.
I think it's cool.
I think it's, oops.
Cool, yeah.
Yes, you're welcome.
Little messages come through.
Happy to help resonate with you.
How's everyone in chat tonight? Okay, so now we're back. Oh, so guys are we is it say 11 or 1?
My vision is blurry. It says 1
Okay
It says 11. I got I don't know
This is one doesn't it I can't double
Sometimes the numbers don't make sense because there's more people talking in the chat and sometimes there's way less people talking in the number.
I don't know. That number really means anything.
When I blur my eyes a little bit, it says 11. I was pretending it says 11. It'll make me more confident. Let me see what it says here.
You know a lot of people are on at the same time. I
Do appreciate you guys
Checking me out, but you know you guys go anywhere you want. You know feel free to
Because it's 13 watching so it must be yeah, and that says 13. Okay
We're fine guys. I
Don't know if it's just light or something but some things of something's obscuring my vision a little bit
Hey, babe, there's Rudy you want to say hi Rudy?
We're gonna say hi to the 13 people in chat. Hi
We're just getting a little bit old I mean he's like
He's really he kind of like is acting like an old man cuz when he got here
He's me. I was like a regular meow now. It's like yeah, it's like it's like a little soft meow
But his his owner told me his former owner told me he's like that's he's always he's like doesn't really meow very much
Yeah, I hear Lenore Lenore's over here, too. Oh, that's tricks right there, too
Come on tricks tricks. He's been talking about Rudy. He talks me out. He wants he gets upset
Yeah, I know hey flirty
Hey tricks
Your mom's cat lived until she was 21. Oh, I hope Rudy does live hope you live well into your 20s
I heard of a cat that lived actually till like 20. I think of record is like 29 years old
So that's pretty long. I'm pretty long life. I mean for a cat, you know, so I bet if you hope you live a long time, Rudy
I know I know you're getting old. I hope you live way past your life
So I think someone at I think we did a trivia question like who's the oldest man in the earth. I think it's I think he's like
129 or something and he's in China
Or he was I think he's passed away
Especially outdoor cats live they live a little much longer. Yeah. Well, it's like
There's they can they can live much longer because they I think they're they are happier when they can go outdoors
And it's like in that but they have that but there's also like a lot more hazards out there. You love Rudy
I really use a sweetheart
Sitting here on this pillow
He's been sitting on he looks to sit on this couch all the time except when he
It's up to P or you or he goes to get a drink or some food. You'd like to be like all cuddled with me all the time
He is very sweet, he's a sweet. He's a very soft cat, too. You should see his fur. It's just completely like soft
It looks like there's like
Comerks in it and you're there Lola you're there too looking at the wall Lola staring at the stuff on the wall
I don't know if you can see it
Or they're looking at the stuff on the wall Lola. Can you see you? There we are
Lenors over here. Lenors come over here Lenors Lenors lately
She's she runs and eats and then she like she's out back on the out back outside
I don't know if she like doesn't like being around other cats or something but hey Lenor come here. Let's stay inside
But also it's been really nice really nice weather there too, and so it's been pretty warm
So maybe the cats like be out in the warm weather. I don't know
They get they go into little funny moods don't they
Hi, you're up there tricks you're sitting up there
Yeah, these are awesome awesome cats very lucky
Yeah, all the other cats I see with you guys are awesome, too
There's she land has so how's your week going it's almost Friday, so you got any plans
I was just on Vida's, Vida's live too.
Cool, here's Flirty Diamonds, Flirty Diamonds is a hi.
Hey Psyche, how's your day going?
Hi, how are you?
I'm doing good, just chilling, smoking right now.
Have you met KZ?
Is that Ben?
Uh, yeah, I'm with KZ.
Oh my god, Ben.
Yeah, I'm just here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I mean, I yeah, he said I I went to the store and bought it and he like he said me
Yeah
Here we go
Women that I've seen it do I seem they'd like to do bombs and I saw another one who does gravity bomb
I don't think I have the
attachment but I think that
I kind of I think there's a separate attachment. I kind of forgot I haven't smoked waxes so long. Yeah, it's cool
I don't think I have the
I just I just like, you know
I did it before I got it a couple times man
I remember that shit was so good, but I had to buy a whole packet of things like a pen
To that heat it up to put it on like it came with all these pieces to make it's a whole complicated thing
You need a whole set to do it
Well, one of my favorite things that I had one of my favorite like weed tools I ever used is called a nectar collector
And what you do is you just take a little piece
You know you love them
It looks like a little like a little glass dick or whatever with like a little
It's like I think a syringe like say the type typical syringe, but it's like a thin it's like a thin tube
It's like, you know, it's kind of like and you so you heat up
It's made of metal you heat that up with like the torch
And then it's like this long thing and then you just put you put some a dab on the on a mirror or something
and it just like gives you a huge hit and they they work really good so yeah um for the
Dabricks there's this one thing that it collects the wax that you put you put the banger inside
it and then you put it in the bong yeah and like I forgot what it's called but there's a green
that makes all there's like a weed brand like that makes all that equipment I remember I had to go
I forget what it's called. It's a big brand though. It makes it all like those accessories for doing dabs and shit.
Yeah, there's a lot of, I think, glass companies are doing really, really well.
And so are the weed companies out in California, because it's awesome, but they know who's not doing
well out here is the illegal growers or illegal vendors because it's like now.
Well, no, they still think they use illegal immigrants
to do the cutting of stuff,
but it's like, you know, it's just like they don't sell,
they don't just like, you know,
they're not just growing like a private person buying
and then selling it to other people,
which is like, you know,
some people were doing that on a larger scale.
Now it's like, you have to pay the tax company,
like the businesses need to be registered
to pay taxes on the weed.
And it's, you know, it can be very expensive too.
Okay, I'm sorry, hold on.
I'll put it back on there.
There we go.
It's up in the middle
I'll be the lucky air tonight. It can be a complicated process and you know
paperwork and
It's just bureaucratic type bullshit and you know, that's in a day people would they get like a
15 foot by 25 foot piece of land in their backyard, you know
And they're dead enough to grow everything you need it
But you know, you should go young food. That's how she used to be, you know
Yeah, now it's like we're so spoiled. I mean, but now it's yeah, now it's this instant gratification
But yeah back in the 80s
I think it was like my my dad's like his best friend lived down the street from us and he wanted to grow we but you know
how my dad like figured it out and
Set up the case of a garden in this guy's yard and all the other all the other older kids with
I'm trying to, sorry, sorry, Casey, Casey, your microphone is like, your microphone sounds like,
can you adjust his mic? Oh, yeah, I can't. Yeah, his mic is terrible. It sounds like it sounds
like it's like, it's like, like burping. I mean, it's like, it sounds like an organ,
xylophone or like a church pipe organ that's burping or something.
Oh God is the first now check one two. It's worse
Yeah, it's I mean, it's like it just sounded a little bit better just not just the second time you talked but um
Yeah, you know, it is worth that
You know, I my everyone was always complaining about my my audio until I got a couple pairs of headphones
And it's like, you know, I just got cheap ones, but they're on Amazon, but
I get I get like a good
pair of Bluetooth that like sound good and then that those are charging. I'm using that a bit. Yeah, I
Got you. Yeah
It sounds like the teacher on the on the peanuts, you know, it's like
I hear your voice but it sounds like that
Sounds a little bit better he man said he mentioned it sounds better. I mean I can I can tolerate it. It's like I have a good ear, but
Yep, now if you could just sound far away. Oh, come on. It's k-shake. It's so funny
Yeah, but we had an interesting we've had interesting day, so yeah today, um, you know Arthur was saying it's like
Really terrible thing. I forgot who he said it to you, but oh, yeah, I think he said it to
Good times and he said
I mean, it's really bad. It's like, you know, the unaliving so like, like, you know, do you put a put a gut, you know
to you and it's like
And I just literally said like to other people and to him on the panel
I was like, please don't stay that and he keeps saying it. It's like so he's just to just be banned
I was like I really want to like
Give him a chance, but it's like I'm like I can't just keep giving chances because I'll look like
You know, it's that I think my words are meaningless if it's just like I just like keep forgiving
I know I can't help it because I like
I mean if it's constantly just you know, give them a little time out just be like you're just thinking on your butt
You're on time out. Yeah, I think is I think I think 25 or 24 hours
But I mean I mean I mean I was I was you know, I was like, you know, I'll just I'll just do it from me
You know, it's like this because it's like
I don't want to do a permanent band, but it's like it's really getting tempted to do permanent bands on the people that keep staying over
I mean even sick came today and was like I apologize. He apologized to beta you apologize to me
I don't think I don't know if he apologized to flurry diamond, but
My god
This is the same next time next time at least you know you can get in the shower
There's underwear big old stream out of it, and then they'll be clean and so everything else
Okay, I don't know what the hell six problem. What's that babe?
But he said I'm gonna take a shit, and I'm gonna show my shitty ass. Oh my god
That's just what he did
That is just obscene good times back home
I am back, yes.
Hi, good to have you.
I'm warning you about a sick dog.
When he first came around, he was bragging about how he could get everybody's channels terminated.
Okay.
So I'm like, I'm letting you know, no, I know, but I hear that from like, I mean, I hear a million people say that, you know
I guess, you know, I don't know
It came out of this old goddamn mouth. I know. I know. I know he said it and I know I
Know I know and it's like that's why it's like, okay, so people are just so determined
Well, you fuck with that that guy in your stream earlier
When I woke up he was trying to get your channel nuked and you didn't realize I had to tell you that
Uh, was, oh yeah, I was looking at the phone or some, or I was looking at something else, um, at the time and then
I don't remember the name though.
Yeah, but, oh yeah, I don't even remember the, yeah, Arthur said something terrible to you and I, I, I, I, I ended the stream with Alita.
But yeah, it was like that.
You said, you said I'm ending the stream with Alita, but you didn't do it until he told you he was trying to get your channel straight.
Well, that's because that's that's when he like showed his cards by by saying that kind of stuff
I mean, it's like but and so now I know but I'm okay. I'll be careful. I mean, it's like, I don't
Watch I'm using a side-eye on some of these some of these people and you know
Beedah said 30 diamond is scared you face her on panel
The story diamond was just on panel with me. I mean
Yeah, I mean, it's why you join
She would she she can go on live and talk shit about me and raging and shit like what on her?
She can go live and do what she wants. I don't do a fuck. I'm not gonna go live about her
Yeah, they don't give fuck about each other
I mean, I mean, I think they do because it's like if you don't really care about somebody then it's like you just like
Have a difference towards
I'm not gonna make about her she can go live and she can talk shit about me talk shit about raising to be a liar
That's on her, but I'm not gonna go on live and rant about her cuz she doesn't she was rents like
I play music
Yeah
Well, that's why it's not really important for monetization for you because it's like, you know
That'd be kind of a difficult thing to do if you were monetized to play a copyright music all the time
But you know what I know how to get away with it. Yeah, I know but I mean as a
Monetized channel it would probably be just a little bit more nervous. I'm not monetized. Yeah
I told her to be
Yeah
Because you know why my chill get newt because I'm playing fucking music
That's why I'm so kind of careful about about interfere your new gas you out of them
Well, my new guest is KZ. So I know KZ. I know untrackable. I know pluridiamen. Hello, everybody
Everybody
Be careful be careful with what you're doing. What's up untrackable you said hello
Hi untrackable. She's going to drop raging demons DMs from
She said, okay good times will never be yeah, well, you know
Good times had some fans. I think good times is a good guy good times is like you're kind of look
Oh, you know kind of like old school kind of like remind me like the kind of like the farmer who got
Drunk on the track the tractor
Tractor I know it's a crab it's sold from the farm I made now
Okay, why no tomatoes this year good times
I couldn't hear that.
Where are the tomatoes this year?
Are there tomatoes?
Hey, Crystal, Marie.
I don't grow tomatoes anymore because I have gastritis.
I have, like, asteriflex.
Crystal, Crystal, I don't know what you're talking about.
You're not perma-band on my panel, Crystal.
You're not performing bands, am I? Did I block you?
I think she was mad you kicked her out the other night or something.
Oh, no, no, I just, I just, I mean, it was, you know, Crystal, you know,
sometimes it gets too crazy on my panel. It's just, I, you know, I get a little bit,
you know, I don't really ban anybody. I ban like a few people, but not, I didn't ban you.
You took my wrench. Yeah. Yeah, she's I doubt I doubt I know I know case if I take a lot of people's wrenches
And you know what there's a no there's a no whining policy about the wrenches. It's just all it is
Other they're all the reds are there for people that want to like help my channel not to like, you know
there are people with been dead, I have to think of all of them.
What do you mean?
I've done nothing to help you channel.
I don't know.
I know, I know, but there's just stuff going on with like, because people,
you know, because certain mods will get like dogs.
You know what the haters get to you.
It's okay though.
I don't know what to do.
I am one time, one time, one time, I made five women, my mods that hate each other
and they went fucking good times.
It drove lots.
It drove a lot.
The second hit mods.
Yeah, I mean, it's like I've seen people just take totally their personality. We were like, why is that person Jen?
Yes, it's crazy
I got two mods now just Jen and
I don't know. I don't know.
You know the reason why I don't make men mods is because they get drunk and they just ban the whole chat
I don't drink I know I drink but I never ban the chat the only problem and my head with me or even anybody else like I don't
Was that she didn't like that I drank cuz she's been sober for like several years like 60 years
Drink all the time do she watches you
She's my mod. Yeah. Oh, no, no, no. Yeah, I know you're talking about just Jen
Okay, I'm I meant I was a mod for Emma Emma has like 25,000 times. You said she was an X what?
She's an X porn star. Well, I didn't know that
Yeah
Interested in me like she's trying to hook up with me or whatever. It's that porn stars. We should say poor porn black
I'm gonna steal it from you good times
So just because you
Think I'm gonna steal her from you go for it. It doesn't matter to me
All right, those boys
Well, this is a pillow. It's a little pig pillow, and it's just
Oh, you put it behind your head?
Yeah.
No.
These are the little pillows.
I was like, what the fuck was that?
That's my only stuff, Dan.
You don't have a clutch or a pulse or anything, do you?
I used to have a I used to click on you and man. We're hanging out there. I'm out though
Well, oh, I won. Yeah, I was Sam and three diamonds. You see three diamond
The three diamond get your uh, that that video or
I don't know. I heard that that you were talking
I haven't been I haven't been on here since 4 a.m. Yeah, so what you guys are up on panel up here last night
Yeah, we had a good panel last night. I think
We're cooking up the content pot pot
Yeah, it was
really good night and
Contractor school because
My my beard is gray, but I saw that the color here. Yeah, but
Offset good time. Good time. You couldn't grow a beard that long like we could no I know I
You haven't seen old pictures of me. I've current some crazy-ass beards before
Hey, that's dedication to let it go that long. I kind of let mine go
Kind of that long once in a while. Some people can't grow beards because it looks stupid
Yeah, she can she can cakes. I can't she can cakes. I'm very
diamond. I wish I had that problem. I mean, I just got the
electric razor for like I got it for like ten bucks with the
edit coupon for it. So, it was like, you know, I bought a I
bought a goddamn the cheapest electric clippers they had from
Walmart.
It was like 15 bucks and I used it twice and it in a fucking
My god, you get what you paid for you're trying to instigate
And you know, I'm not gonna play dumb with you. You know what instigate?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, it's like I mean, I don't but it's like you know some people do like some people I don't find the drama like that
They're training but a lot of people that they that's what they're gonna let things happen naturally and organically
It just shows up it shows up I just I don't I don't I don't like you know go looking for I mean when I started started
You like it wouldn't get people on your stream they y'all each other, don't you?
Not like you don't like when they yell each other. I don't like when they docked
I don't like when they threaten or use racial language, but I don't mind if they have a debate
I know I kick people off all the time
I kick people off my panel all the time and and warren and I have the rules posted I did
I do everything I can basically you can't like just I get other than like going into people's mouths and
tying
A bow around their tongue. There's one thing I gotta do to psyche. You never gave in
He always let whoever he wanted up on Pam. He never gave into the pressures of everybody else
So I'll give that to you. Thank you, man. Thank you. How's monkey? Oh, who's monkey?
Who does some have an animal name monkey before you're doing? I'm sorry. I said the name someone said in chat
I'm sorry. I didn't mean I didn't mean to like say something personal. I was monkey my cat my cats. Okay. Yeah, okay
It says you kick them saki, but a lot of back-up shumis.
And each came Memphis, I get amnesia sometimes.
I can't stay mad at things like that, like that.
It's like I just can't stay that mad,
and then I start feeling bad that I miss the people.
Okay, so cakes is referring, okay, I got you, I got you, I got you.
No, I got a cigarette butt here, I'm gonna finish.
Okay.
Wait, what is the armist discord Brigade? What is that? Oh, you're talking about the the discord Brigade
No, no, no, no, no
Hey, that's as has a lot of wild theories. I mean they call it
What's the guys they call it some other name? I forgot the name they call it, but they call it something discord
Discord Brigade, I think it's just a myth. I think it's like no, there's no meth
They actually all go on discord and try to get people's channels fucked up. Oh
Well, are you part of that?
Are you part of that? Are you on are you in are you in the
Yes, I will judge you for you are you in the discord? I don't even know that is I don't this would you know
I'm not even in your discord
If I was going to be in discord, I'd be in yours so I could talk to you.
I'm in Alicia's with you.
I see you posting this sometimes.
If you're going to be a streamer.
I saw you posting it the other morning.
Well, I mean, I haven't, but I haven't set up just so it announces my show.
There's people on my show, but I'm not even, I'm never in it.
I just use it for the email.
Yeah, I'm not even in your discord.
Don't you have a discord?
Will you guys all talk?
You know who could mean any single person on the face of earth is like seven and a half billion of us
What are you talking about? I think there's just like one five billion people. There's eight billion people on the earth actually
Why did I say that I don't know why that number came to my mind
But it's just a small number, I don't know, maybe you're thinking of the population of China, I think China is actually there.
Maybe I'm thinking that's what it should be.
You know that, right?
What's up?
I said, who could mean all the people on the guy in the face there?
Yeah, I mean, it's like the Georgia guide stones, right? It's like, you know, get the earth down.
Hey, what's up with that though? Who took those down?
I
You guys can figure out if you like, you know
Okay
Okay, it's a it's a it's a it's a chicken cakes. Okay. Yeah
Hey chicken cakes
Casey's fuck. Okay. You kind of look you kind of like who's so Marie's like like twin sisters
I'm doing fantastically fantastic. No, it's literally me. I'm not
It's just being like it's just being here we go
Alright, Mr. You guys Mr. Bees is here. We have a celebrity guest. Mr. Hey, uh, psych psych psych
Sure
Request of my boyfriend
So good times used to be a prominent streamer used to the streamer right what happened good times
What are you streaming? Where's your channel?
You don't even know about my
Are you back are you gonna make a new channel this channel's from
Joe, can you keep up with the conversation, sir? Joe shipply
Joe's
You're lucky you have a nice you won't pour him by me. All right, so you won't
He's poor on me, he's poor on me, I'm just.
He's poor on me, but he does like to say things
that are against you.
He showed you his balls, he showed you his balls one night
and then.
That's Aldi, that's not him.
Yeah, I said Aldi, oh yeah, no, no, Joe is not him.
I said Aldi.
I was talking about Joe, Joe's OK.
So you gotta watch what he says.
You gotta watch what he says.
His name is Brillium.
Is your name Brillium?
Brillium?
Yeah.
And don't forget, what mom am I?
What mom am I from what show?
What mom?
Oh, yeah.
Chicken cakes.
Chicken cakes looks like the mom from Malcolm in the Middle.
Yeah.
That's what he said.
I think that was a little bit.
Like, why is it like you're talking to yourself?
Have you ever seen Lois?
Do you know who Lois is?
Lois?
From Family Guy?
I know that bitch.
Family Guy.
Lois from, uh, it's Lois from Malcolm in the Middle.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I should show a virgin
Can you see leave my boyfriend alone? He said he's Virginia for me leave him alone. Okay. Good times
Is he saying that you he's a virgin? I didn't hear what he said
You say it's a joke
He's mad because
I don't know. I don't know.
the
There's looking at me. I just I shaved my beard. I think I have no I just I just kind of coming back
No, I just I shaved it just so I wouldn't I wouldn't look so old because I was like I looked like I was like
Like I could look at you and be like, okay, this is that you can't look at me like that though I'm 27
You can't ever tell me that 27 she's 72. Yeah, we put those numbers around your 27 years. I think she's my birthday was on Sunday, so I met 27. You're halfway there. You're halfway there.
My birthday was on Sunday now. I'm 50 fuck all you guys
Shit
I think you're like my husband's age at times
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry a trackable. I know it's not always
What do you mean?
You just call chicken cakes whenever you uh, whenever you think about your husband. Do you ever think about good time?
With the woman and you're thinking about a different woman while you're fucking her because yet
That's the way you have to keep a heart and that's Gucci is all hell
I was thinking about
when I was fucking my girlfriend, I yelled Steve, like Steve, please.
It's like, hey, what are you yelling for?
What's going on with Joe?
Is he getting dick down?
And he's like, Steve.
No, I'm actually looking at you.
She's burning me gay.
Look at you.
She's actually making it.
You have to kick him.
He's back.
Yeah.
Chicken cake, chicken cakes.
So Joe.
So, um, yeah, joking about the closet. Uh, he, he's in love with flirty diamond now.
He said, he said, he said he wanted to put anal beads, anal beads in and pull them out of the sea.
No, so, uh, psych.
Yeah, how do you like how do you like streaming with a good time? She's one of the a long-time podcaster?
I can have you like a foreign diplomat in in my chat in my panels
Yeah
Arthur you're in trouble Arthur
Joker's fucking of the illegitimate child was on the back of a stream as in his camera
Stream this to your audience, I don't know. Yeah, then it will go on your channel. It will stream my
I think I'm gonna ask you to log in maybe I'm not sure 100% I don't appreciate that
I'll go to like people's places. We don't care. What is she talking about?
Good I'm a streamer. Are you?
What you're on a stream
What are you talking about?
Yeah, I guess I have an option.
Because everybody has been on Psyche's stream,
and I felt that I wanted to come here and say hi to Psyche.
And hi to you and your stupid overalls
without a shirt, you jerk.
And I love me some Clirty Diamond.
And yes, Mr. Beast, AKA Joker, always good.
And I never got to hang out with Psyche.
Did I forget about Joe? Oh I love Joe. I forgot about Joe.
Joe? Who's Joe? Who's Joe? I've never heard of that person.
Oh yeah. No, that's my state. Joe is Joe. You're never good.
I didn't think that gang is not ever. But I've never heard of him though.
I don't know. I don't get it.
That's it. That's it. That's it.
Yeah, I got it. He's he's he's
he's not banned. He's he's he's
he's he's he's he's he's he's
I'm not going to be able to
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, the other night. Oh, I remember that night. Oh, yeah
So what the other night would happen was I had this this guy
I know probably from like 15 years or something like that
He said date my one of my friends and then another broke it up and he he had a
Baby a few couple years ago with the woman and then they broke up. Okay, so then he comes over and he's like now
He said he said hey, do you have a he said say hey, well first you said hey, he said hey
Do you want to watch me fuck my my girl or like my you know, my my
Sound like you want you wanted to have a threesome
Well, yeah, he's like he's not a good watch and I was like I was like, okay
But he wanted me to buy like a charger for his DMT pen so we could like smoke DMT and stuff
And I was like, okay, sure we're gonna hang out and so
And so I went and we got the charger. I didn't buy it and I'm buying it
but we got the Charles say we got the charger and
Came back here, and then I was like we're just like you smoked a little DMT, and we're just hanging out and then
He like he's like wait. He's like, oh, he's okay. He's like, he's like, he's like, I was like, I was so warm or up
Okay, anyway, so Joe, okay, you just listen backstage Joe, you'll have a smile. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, I'll story Joe Joe loves to interrupt and that's he knows it noise the shit out of me
Okay
Where did the DMC pen?
They she has it. I guess he he sells DMT or something like that
So we came back and so but I was like I was like I've been told people before is like
Oh, you can like watch us have sex or whatever and they never do they always just end up closing the door like and I don't really care
I'm not like not really that into like
Sitting in the corner like watching but I kind of like have a crush on this guy
So I was like, okay, okay, and so they went he went in the room with her and he left the door open and so then I
It was not like I don't mind stories like this
Yeah, you know, you know fucking
Joker Joker had a threesome with a woman. Her name was Alice
Yeah
It's just real quick it's real quick so there's no I heard them so then I heard them having sex
I heard like I heard like I heard like a smacky sound. I heard like a suction kind of sound
I was just sitting here watching listen to music and then
I was like, okay. And then it's like, so it's over. And then he's like, he's like,
hey, John, he's like, do you want to come hit this? And, uh, and it was, you know,
like they had the DMT pipe in there or something. So